

ABOUT

After completing <u>my PhD</u> in Robotics and Computer Science, I introduced my love of music and sound into my practice. I'm the attracted by technical aspect of sound and music, since see all of these inextricably linked and also love the creative side technology and programming. In the last few years, I have specialized myself in web development and worked as a full-stack engineer. You can see some of my latest work in my portfolio.

CONTACT

- **♀** Granada (Spain)
- in LinkedIn profile
- github.com/valeiras
- ✓ d.r.valeiras@gmail.com

David Reverter Valeiras

Doctor of Engineering - Front End Developer

EDUCATION

PhD in Computer Science

Université Pierre et Marie Curie (Paris)

Master Degree in advanced Systems and Robotics Université Pierre et Marie Curie (Paris)

Industrial Engineering, Specialty: Mechanics
E.T.S.E.I. de Vigo (Vigo)

Live Sound Technician

Centro de formación escénica de Andalucía

SKILLS

Programming languages:

TS	Typescript	JS	Javascript			
目	HTML	ş	Python			
9	C++	티	CSS			
Tools:						
		015.				
	Node.js	₩	React			

Languages:

Matlab

Git

Spanish	Native	English	Fluent
Galician	Native	French	Fluent

EXPERIENCE

2023-2024: Full-stack developer

Ennubo (Madrid)

Next.js

Arduino

2022-2023: Developer of Mekanika

Cabeza Patata(London)

2020-2022: Live Sound Technician

Freelance

2017-2020: Professional musician

Freelance

2013-2017: Doctorate

Institut de la Vision (Paris)